<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>The hungarian man who went to Malta</title>
    <link>https://thmwwtm.github.io/</link>
    <description>Recent content on The hungarian man who went to Malta</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 21 Feb 2021 09:02:00 +0200</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://thmwwtm.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Finding a home</title>
      <link>https://thmwwtm.github.io/posts/20210221_rent/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 21 Feb 2021 09:02:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://thmwwtm.github.io/posts/20210221_rent/</guid>
      <description>First of all the culture of the real estate agents is much better here than at home. At least what I experienced. I asked three agents to look for a new home for us. All of them gave me multiple possibilities and looked for new ones immediately if I didn&amp;rsquo;t like the first. They took me from door to door, by own car, paying a quite expensive Bolt ride and once (it was my first week) I asked if we can go by bus, so I try that too, and she insisted on paying my ticket.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Transportation</title>
      <link>https://thmwwtm.github.io/posts/20210108_transport_part_1/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 08 Jan 2021 09:02:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://thmwwtm.github.io/posts/20210108_transport_part_1/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;rsquo;ve worked abroad for quite some time. I got used to traveling. I made it easy for myself. I do not have too much stuff and I do not require too much to feel comfortable or at least &amp;ldquo;ok&amp;rdquo;.
But now I am not alone what makes the relocation a bit more difficult.
My partner has ten times more luggage than I, and our dog can not be moved by airplane.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Introduction</title>
      <link>https://thmwwtm.github.io/posts/20201218_intro/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 18 Dec 2020 09:02:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://thmwwtm.github.io/posts/20201218_intro/</guid>
      <description>Who writes it why and what will be here?
If the title does not ring a bell you need to see this:   Who I am a software developer from Hungary. After a while I felt the urge to leave my current enterprise position, and for some time already I had the idea to maybe try something abroad.
I started to work with software somewhere in high school, then I was intern, worked at small company, startup incubator, startup, bigger company and enterprise.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
