<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on The hungarian man who went to Malta</title>
    <link>https://thmwwtm.github.io/posts/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on The hungarian man who went to Malta</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 27 Mar 2021 09:02:00 +0200</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://thmwwtm.github.io/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Github actions from zero to this blog</title>
      <link>https://thmwwtm.github.io/posts/20210327_github_actions/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 27 Mar 2021 09:02:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://thmwwtm.github.io/posts/20210327_github_actions/</guid>
      <description>I wanted to try Github actions since it got announced. Finally I had it on my foreseeable list when I started this blog, and lately, I did it. 👏 🎉🎆 I got to a working pipeline in 25 tries, lets go through each step how it improved piece by piece.
 I started to work on it at night, thinking it would not take long. (hehe, famous last words). After around 20 failed runs, I went to sleep.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How this site is made</title>
      <link>https://thmwwtm.github.io/posts/20210322_gohugo_ghpages/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 22 Mar 2021 09:02:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://thmwwtm.github.io/posts/20210322_gohugo_ghpages/</guid>
      <description>I wanted to try gohugo for a long time now, as I wanted to do more go stuff, even if it is just using it. Also, hugo has quite good benchmarks. (And luckily I need to use some go at work)
Other points I wanted to fulfill:
 use GitHub pages (static) use markdown for editing  and hugo is good for both.
I wanted to use markdown because I like to write docs in md, and I don&amp;rsquo;t need an editor for that, I can do it on my phone, or any computer.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Transportation part 2, the receiving end</title>
      <link>https://thmwwtm.github.io/posts/20210307_transport_part_2/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 07 Mar 2021 09:02:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://thmwwtm.github.io/posts/20210307_transport_part_2/</guid>
      <description>Logistics lvl 9000+ The monthly schedule of the transportation company was on 27th February, meaning they arrive to Malta on 1st March at night, and they collect the packages days before departure. Before I left we already had a lot of boxes filled, but my partner had another lot of left. On 25th of February the package collection happened.
   View this post on Instagram         A post shared by thmwwtm (@thmwwtm)</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Finding a home</title>
      <link>https://thmwwtm.github.io/posts/20210221_rent/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 21 Feb 2021 09:02:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://thmwwtm.github.io/posts/20210221_rent/</guid>
      <description>First of all the culture of the real estate agents is much better here than at home. At least what I experienced. I asked three agents to look for a new home for us. All of them gave me multiple possibilities and looked for new ones immediately if I didn&amp;rsquo;t like the first. They took me from door to door, by own car, paying a quite expensive Bolt ride and once (it was my first week) I asked if we can go by bus, so I try that too, and she insisted on paying my ticket.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Transportation</title>
      <link>https://thmwwtm.github.io/posts/20210108_transport_part_1/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 08 Jan 2021 09:02:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://thmwwtm.github.io/posts/20210108_transport_part_1/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;rsquo;ve worked abroad for quite some time. I got used to traveling. I made it easy for myself. I do not have too much stuff and I do not require too much to feel comfortable or at least &amp;ldquo;ok&amp;rdquo;.
But now I am not alone what makes the relocation a bit more difficult.
My partner has ten times more luggage than I, and our dog can not be moved by airplane.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Introduction</title>
      <link>https://thmwwtm.github.io/posts/20201218_intro/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 18 Dec 2020 09:02:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://thmwwtm.github.io/posts/20201218_intro/</guid>
      <description>Who writes it why and what will be here?
If the title does not ring a bell you need to see this:   Who I am a software developer from Hungary. After a while I felt the urge to leave my current enterprise position, and for some time already I had the idea to maybe try something abroad.
I started to work with software somewhere in high school, then I was intern, worked at small company, startup incubator, startup, bigger company and enterprise.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
